Guide to the American Labor Conference on International Affairs Records TAM.038
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series II. Office Files, 1940-1947, nd
  - Wille, Werner, "The Role of American Labor in the Solution of Problems of International Education After the War," April 1944. 7pp. (2 copies) - "Paper drafted for research use by ALCIA officials" (Box 23, Folder 21)
    Film R-7124, Reel 24: Frame XVI:B:82
  - Wille, Werner, "A Survey of Educational Planning in the United States and Various Other Countries, 8l pp. - "Paper drafted for research use by ALCIA officials", undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
    Film R-7124, Reel 24: Frame XVI:B:83
  - Pendle Hill Conferences, May 6, 1943-Jul 2, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 24: Frame XVI:B:84
  - Personnel Applications, Feb 19, 1943-Jul 8, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Film R-7124, Reel 24: Frame XVI:B:85
  - Plans for & General Meeting, Feb 8, 1943-Jun 1943 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Film R-7124, Reel 24: Frame XVI:B:86
  - Poland-A Test Case, Sep 29, 1944-Nov 1944 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 24: Frame XVI:B:87
  - Political Committee, Jan 30, 1943-Apr 1945 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 24: Frame XVI:B:88
  - Postwar Information Exchange, Jul 13, 1944-Apr 11, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 24: Frame XVI:B:89
  - Princeton Conference on Full Employment, Jun 16, 1944-Jul 1944 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:B:90
  - Projects, ca.Jun 1945 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:B:91
  - Radio Speeches, Jul 24, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:B:92
  - Reports of ALCIA, Jan 1, 1945-Jan 1, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:B:93
  - Salvemini, Gaetano, Feb 4, 1943-Jun 12, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:B:94
  - Senate Special Committee on Policy and Planning, Apr 28, 1943-Dec 8, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:B:95
  - Statement on the first year of ALCIA, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:B:96
  - Taxes, Jan 21, 1944-Dec 7, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:B:97
  - Union Contract, Mar 22, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:B:98
  - Union for Democratic Action, Aug 13, 1943-May 21, 1946, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:B:99
  - Meeting with Jan Stanczyk, May 17, 1944, ca.Apr 1944-May 1944 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:B:100
  - Manuscripts for Free Labor Contains: - "Can Labor Surrender Its Right to Strike?" 2pp. (3 copies) - "Congress Caught in Anti-Labor Eddy," 2pp. (3 copies) - "The Government's Wage and Price Policy," 2pp. (2 copies) - "Labor Elections in Germany," 2pp. (3 copies) - "Labor's Executive Council Meets," 2pp. (2 copies) - "The Problem of Italian Trade Unionism," 3pp. (3 copies) p - "The Reconstruction of the Austrian Trade Unions," 2 pp. (2 copies) - "Set the World Free, American Labor Urges," 2pp. (3 copies) - "Tax Reduction the Wrong Way," 2pp. (2 copies), undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:B:101
  - Drafts for International Bulletin Contains: - "Belgium Ties Wages to Index of Production," 2pp. (2 copies) - "German Unions, Smashed by Nazis, Revived in Berlin," 2pp. (2 copies) - "Social Democrats Win in Vienna Shop Elections," 2pp. (2 copies) - "Unity Parleys Broken Off in Norway and Denmark," 2pp. (2 copies), Oct 1945 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:B:102
- Series III. Modern Review, 1939-1950, nd
  - Correspondence, A, May 5, 1947-Sep 25, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, B, Jan 7, 1946-Jun 12, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:2
  - Correspondence, C, Jan 2, 1947-Mar 31, 1950, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:3
  - Speakers Manual, undated, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, D, Feb 19, 1945-Jan 27, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:4
  - Correspondence, Distribution, Feb 15, 1947-Feb 3, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:5
  - Correspondence, E, Feb 11, 1947-Nov 13, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:6
  - Correspondence, F, Jan 24, 1947-Jul 19, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:7
  - Correspondence, G, Dec 9, 1946-May 1, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:8
  - Correspondence, H-I, Jan 28, 1947-Jul 28, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:9
  - Correspondence, Interoffice, Jan 30, 1947-Mar 15, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:10
  - Correspondence, J-K, Mar 25, 1947-Sep 28, 1950, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:11
  - Correspondence, L, Jan 20, 1947-Mar 21, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:12
  - Correspondence, M, Jan 9, 1946-Jan 13, 1950, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:13
  - Correspondence, N-0, Jan 23, 1947-Jun 27, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:14
  - Correspondence, P, Jan 18, 1947-Feb 1, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:15
  - Correspondence, Promotion and Publicity, Apr 3, 1947-Oct 20, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:16
  - Correspondence, R, Dec 14, 1946-Jun 8, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:17
  - Correspondence, S, Dec 5, 1946-Jul 12, 1950, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:18
  - Correspondence, T, Apr 2, 1947-Jan 13, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:19
  - Correspondence, U-V, Apr 8, 1947-Jul 25, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 25: Frame XVI:C:20
  - Correspondence, WXYZ, Dec 17, 1946-Oct 24, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Daniel Bell, Jun 2, 1947, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:22
  - Correspondence with Trade Unionists, Apr 11, 1947, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:23
  - Contributing Editors List, Dec 19, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:24
  - Copyrights, 1947-1949 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Form Letters, Dec 9, 1947-Feb 1949, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:25
  - Hook's People, Oct 26, 1947-Feb 3, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:26
  - Press Releases, Oct 4, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:27
  - Statement, Vol. 1, no. 1, Mar 1947 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:28
  - Abramovitch, Raphael R., "From Socialist Utopia to Totalitarian 'Realism'," 28pp. (2 copies), Jun 1947 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:29
  - Alexander, Robert J., "Military Dictatorship in Latin America," l3pp., undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:30
  - Arendt, Hannah, "The Rights of Man," l6pp., undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:31
  - Blum, Leon, "The Last Month," 28pp., Jan 1950 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:32
  - Blum Leon, "Socialist or Managerial Revolution?" l4 pp. (2 copies), Apr 1947 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:33
  - Blum Leon, "Whose Fault," 3pp., Aug 1947 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:34.)
  - Braunthal, Alfred, "An Economy of Autonomous Forces and its Problems," 17pp., Mar 1947 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:35
  - Braunthal, Alfred, "A Slow Start on the Road to Full Employment Policy," l7 pp., Jan 1950 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:36
  - Brailsford, H. N., "England's Economic Crisis," l3pp. (2 copies), Apr 1947 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:37
  - Brockway, Fenner, "Visit to a German Hospital," 6pp., May 1947 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:38
  - Calas, Nicolas, "Are The Germans Paranoiacs?" l5pp., Jun 1947 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:39
  - Childs, John, "American Liberalism Today," ll pp., Mar 1947 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:40
  - Cork, Jim, "Portrait of Einstein," 9pp., Aug 1947 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:41
  - Cork, Jim, "Portrait of Nehru," 9pp., Apr 1947 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:42
  - Denicke, George, "Challenge of Conquest," l3 pp. (2 copies), Mar 1947 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:43
  - Dubinsky, David, "You Can't Legislate Maturity: Reply of an American Union Leader to the Proposed Anti-Labor Bills," 23pp., Apr 1943 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:44
  - Editorials Contains: - "A Not-So-Innocent Abroad," 5pp. (2 copies) - "The Desire for Chaos," 3pp. (2 copies) - "Elections in the Pickwickian Sense," 3pp. (2 copies) - "Free But Divided," 3pp. - "Freedom For The Thought We Hate," 4pp. - "French Interlude," 4pp. - "Frenchman's Burden," 3pp. (2 copies) - "French Socialists and the Fourth Republic," 3pp. (2 copies) - "From Julian Gorkin," 40pp. - "Germany SOS," 3pp. - "John L. Outflanks the Bureaucrats," 3pp. - "The Law and Order of Chaos," l p. (2 copies) - "Law Without Justice," 3pp. - "March of Moscow Time," 4 pp. - "Miners, Too, Are People," 4 pp. (2 copies) - "Miner Victory," 3pp. - "Mixed-Up Economy," 3pp. - "The NAM Takes Its Revenge," 2pp. - "Peace Treaties or Peace?" 3pp. (2 copies) - "Robbing the Pillars," 3pp. (2 copies) - "Sanctions Against Monaco," 3pp. (2 copies) - "Secrets of Yalta," 4pp. (2 copies) - "Supermen or Super-Robots?" 4pp. - "Tight Rope Act," 2pp. - "Tovarisch Tepliakov Tips His Hand," 4pp. - "Women Talk Too Much," 2pp. (2 copies), 1947 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:45
  - Faravelli, Giuseppe, "The Crisis in Italian Socialism," 7pp. (3 copies-1 in Italian), Mar 1947 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:46
  - Fischer, Louis, "Mahatma Gandhi and Generalissimo Stalin," l3pp., Mar 1947 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:47
  - Five Pictures of Germany (International Press) Aug 1947 Contains: - "The 'Normal' Consumer," 5pp. (2 copies) - "Germany-A Rubble Heap," 2pp. (2 copies) - "Sovietization of a German Province," 3pp. (2 copies) - "A Trip Into Germany's Eastern Zone," 3pp. (2 copies) - "Potato Hunt," 3pp. (2 copies) (Box 28, Folder 20)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:48
  - Gelo and Andrea, "France's Four-Year Plan: Its Motive and Meaning," 18pp. (2 copies), Aug 1947 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:49
  - Gross, Feliks, "The Planner and the Planned," (Unpublished). 16pp. nd, undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:50
  - Guttman, Josef, "Limits of Terror," l4pp. (2 copies) April 1947., Apr 1947 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:51
  - Halpern, Ben, "The Israeli Commune: Privacy and the Collective Life," 21pp. nd, undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:52
  - Hart, Stephen, "America Through Soviet Eyes," l6pp., Jun 1947 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:53.)
  - Hicks, Granville, "The Revival of Liberalism," ll pp., Jan 1950 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:54.)
  - Hilferding, Rudolf, "State Capitalism or Totalitarian State Economy," 9pp., Jun 1947 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:55.)
  - Himmelfarb, Gertrude, "The Hero As Politician," ll pp., May 1949 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:56.)
  - Horlitz, "Marx's Definition of Capitalism," l7pp., May 1949 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:57.)
  - Hutchison, Keith, "Britain's Crisis and the Truman Doctrine," l7pp., Jul 1947 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:58.)
  - International Press Clippings Contains: - "America Through European Eyes," 19pp. (2 copies) - "Between Hope and Despair," 6pp. - "Brave New World," 5pp. (3 copies) - "The Cost of British Reconstruction," 3pp. - "French Plan for Reconstruction," 2pp. (3 copies) - "French Syndicalism (or the French Union Movement) in 1947." 1l pp. - "From Spain by Salvador de Madariaga," 3pp. - "A German Re-evaluates Marxism," 4pp. - "Italian Socialist Split in Retrospect," 5pp. - "Nationalization in Britain: Three Views," 6pp. - "Russia's Internal Crisis," 20pp. - "Soul Searching on the French Left," 4pp. (2 copies) - "Stalin's Secret Army," 4pp. (2 copies) - "What Is Justice?" l0 pp. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:59
  - Jacoby, Henry, "Can Capitalism Survive In One Country?" l7pp., Jul 1947 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:60
  - Kecskemeti, Paul, "Existentialism: A New Trend in Philosophy," 20pp., Mar 1947 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:61
  - Kecskemeti, Paul, "Ideology and Class Consciousness," (Unpublished), l3pp., undated (Box 29, Folder 4, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:62
  - Kecskemeti, Paul, "Some Recent Attempts to Define Meaning," ll pp., May 1949 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:63
  - Kecskemeti, Paul, "Timeless History," 8pp., Jun 1947 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:64
  - Kolarz, Walter, "Russian Colonisation," l6pp., May 1947 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:65
  - Kolarz, Walter, "Russian Colonisation II," l7pp., Aug 1947 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:66
  - Korine, Karim, "The middle East-World Storm Center," l5pp. (2 copies), Jul 1947 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:67
  - Krivitsky, W. G., "Stalin's Hand in Spain," 2pp., Apr 15, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:68
  - Levenstein, Aaron, "The Drift Toward Depression," 9pp., Apr 1947 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:69
  - Levenstein, Aaron, "What's In Store For Labor?" 16pp., Jun 1947 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:70
  - List, Kurt, "Fate of the Artist in America," l3pp., May 1947 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:71
  - Lobbenberg, George, "German Cartels Today," 8pp., Aug 1947 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:72
  - Madeira, Mrs. Percy C., [Critique of Dean's Russia-Menace or Promise], Sep 10, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:73
  - Maier, Josef, "Jaspers and German Guilt," 6pp., Aug 1947 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:74
  - Margolin, Julius, "Crime and Punishment," 28pp., undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:75
  - Menck, Clara, "Problems of German Re-education," ll pp. (3 copies), Aug 1947 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:76
  - Meyer, Peter, "Reply to Leon Blum," 7pp., Jun 1947 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:77
  - Modigliani, Franco, "Symposium on Full Employment," 8pp., Jun 1947 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:78
  - Monatte, Pierre, "Trends in French unionism," l3pp., Aug 1947 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:79
  - Narayan, Jayaprakash, "Indian Plan For Socialism," l2pp., Jul 1947 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:80
  - Paechter, Henry M., "Stalingrad-As Seen from the Kremlin," 5pp., Jun 1947 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:81
  - Rieff, Philip, "A Jesuit Looks At Proudhon," 4pp., Jan 1950 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:82
  - Roskolenko, Harry, "Letter From Japan," 3pp., Jul 1947 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:83
  - Sahl, Hans, "From Caligari to Hitler," 5pp. (3 copies-1 in German), Aug 1947 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:84
  - Sapir, Boris, "Is War With Russia Inevitable? An Examination of Burnham's New Thesis," 10 pp., Jul 1947 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:85
  - Saxon, George, "From the Miner's Point of View," l4pp. (2 copies), Aug 1947 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:86
  - Schmidt, Kurt, "Freedom and Bureaucracy," 4pp. (2 copies), Apr 1947 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:87
  - Schwarz, Solomon, "Nationality Policies in the Soviet Union," 27pp., undated (Box 29, Folder 30)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:88
  - Schwarz, Solomon, "Trade Unions in Postwar Russia," l3pp., Jul 1947 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:89
  - Seers, Dudley, "An Economy in Transition," l5 pp., Apr 1947 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:90
  - Serge, Victor, "Socialism and Psychology," l4pp. (2 copies-1 in French), May 1947 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:91
  - Shuster, George N., "Germany and the Future of Europe," l0 pp., May 1947 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:92
  - Steinberg, Julien, "Institutions of Work and Society," 8pp., Jul 1947 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:93
  - Vorrink, Koos, "Holland's New Labour Party," 6pp. (2 copies), Jul 1947 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:94
  - Wolfe, Bernard, "Ecstatic in Blackface: The Negro as a Song-And-Dance Man," 30pp., Jan 1950 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:95
  - Wolfe, Bertram D., "Journey to the Dark Side of the Moon," 7pp., May 1947 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    Film R-7124, Reel 26: Frame XVI:C:96
- Series IV: Clippings on Labor Topics, 1944-1945
  - Clippings, Jan 1944 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, Feb 1944 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, Mar 1944 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, Apr 1944 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, May 1944 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, Jun 1944 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, Jul 1944 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, Aug 1944 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, Sep 1944 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, Oct 1944 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, Nov 1944 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, Jan 1945-Feb 1945 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, Mar 1945 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, Apr 1945-May 1945 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, Jul 1945 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Clippings: Newsletter clips on foreign labor movements, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Series V: Fragile Originals
  - Fragile Originals from Box 16, Folder 3 through Box 16, Folder 4 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 16, Folder 5 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 16, Folder 6 through Box 16, Folder 8 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 16, Folder 9 - part 1 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 16, Folder 9 - part 2 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 17, Folder 1 through Box 17, Folder 12 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 17, Folder 14 through Box 18, Folder 2 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 18, Folder 3 through Box 18, Folder 10 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 19, Folder 1 through Box 19, Folder 11 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 20, Folder 1 through Box 20, Folder 14 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 20, Folder 15 through Box 21, Folder 3 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 21, Folder 4 through Box 21, Folder 7 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 22, Folder 11 through Box 22, Folder 14 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 23, Folder 1 through Box 23, Folder 4 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 23, Folder 11 through Box 24, Folder 1 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 24, Folder 2 through Box 24, Folder 7 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 25, Folder 5 through Box 25, Folder 12 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 25, Folder 13 through Box 26, Folder 2 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 26, Folder 3 through Box 26, Folder 7 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 26, Folder 8 through Box 26, Folder 12 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 27, Folder 1 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 27, Folder 2 through Box 27, Folder 7 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 27, Folder 8 through Box 27, Folder 15 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 28, Folder 1 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 28, Folder 4 through Box 28, Folder 5 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 28, Folder 7 through Box 28, Folder 15 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 28, Folder 17 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 28, Folder 18 through Box 28, Folder 22 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 28, Folder 23 through Box 28, Folder 24 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 29, Folder 1 - part 1 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 29, Folder 1 - part 1 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 29, Folder 2 through Box 29, Folder 17 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Fragile Originals from Box 29, Folder 18 through Box 29, Folder 38 (Box 34, Folder 9)